https://www.twnpnews.com/privacy-policy/

Column ApplicationHomePrivacy PolicyquestionSite FeedbackTWNP ApplicationTWNP Poll ArchiveTWNPNews.com Forums Connect with us
Privacy Policy
TWNPNews Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from twnpnews.com (the “Site”).PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECTWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”We collect Device Information using the following technologies:“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.“Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.“Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to: Communicate with you; Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store–you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.You can opt out of targeted advertising by:GOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymousAdditionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.DO NOT TRACK Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.YOUR RIGHTS If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.MINORS The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 13.CHANGES We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.CONTACT US For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at webmaster@twnpnews.com or by mail using the details provided below: Follow Us
Facebook
Twitter
Headlines
Trending
NXTNXT Announce New Year’s Evil Show, Finn Balor To Defend NXT Title
AEWAEW Announce Holiday Special Events, Snoop Dogg Appearing
WWEGoldberg Teases Match With Roman Reigns
AEWKenny Omega Appears On IMPACT Wrestling, Big Announcement Set For AEW Dynamite
AEWTony Khan, Tony Schiavone Appear On IMPACT Wrestling
AEWShaquille O’Neal Set To Appear On AEW Dynamite
WWELana Vs Nia Jax Set For WWE Raw
WWEJaxson Ryker Resurfaces On WWE Main Event
NJPWIWGP US Title Challenge Match Set For NJPW Detonation
NXTCandice LeRae Injured At NXT TakeOver: WarGames
NXTShirai Vs Ripley NXT Women’s Title Match Set For Next Week
NXTNorth American Title Changes Hands On NXT
AEWPAC Returns On AEW Dynamite
AEWShaquille O’Neal In-Ring Debut Teased On AEW Dynamite
WWEZelina Vega Released By WWE
AEWAEW World Title Match Set For December 2nd Dynamite
WWEWWE Championship Changes Hands On WWE Raw
AEWWill Hobbs Joins Team Taz On AEW Dynamite
Wrestling NewsGridiron and Wrestling: The Football Stars That Made it Big in WWE
WWEChelsea Green Injured Following SmackDown DebutWWE 2 Hotty Works NXT Live Event, Note on CM Punk Chants, Lilian GarciaWrestling News 5 Minutes with Angle, Sting’s Final Wrestling Appearance in the UK, Xplosion
WWE Brock Lesnar Vs Seth Rollins Rematch Set For SummerSlam
Wrestling News Weekly Wrestling Ratings Tracker Update
